[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Canada, the United States and China are three countries whose total area is approximately 12 million sq km.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Virgil Cole, in the 2008 movie Appaloosa, who or what likes a dead buffalo?", "correct_answer": "Everything that eats meat", "incorrect_answers": ["Cattlemen", "Vultures", "Coyotes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Mitchies friend at the camp in the movie Camp Rock?", "correct_answer": "Caitlyn", "incorrect_answers": ["Ella", "Shane", "Tess Tyler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Framingham Heart Study concluded that moderate drinkers were 50 % less likely to die from coronary diseases than this group of people.", "correct_answer": "Non drinkers", "incorrect_answers": ["Heavy drinkers", "Drug addicts", "Stressed persons"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What American actress stars in the 2009 romantic comedy movie The Ugly Truth?", "correct_answer": "Katherine Heigl", "incorrect_answers": ["Ellen Pompeo", "Sandra Bullock", "Alicia Silverstone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Billy Zane from Titanic got a secondary role in Back to the Future as one of Biffs thugs for this reason.", "correct_answer": "The production personal liked his Jetsons t-shirt.", "incorrect_answers": ["He was willing to work for free.", "His father owns Universal Studios.", "His uncle is Bob Gale."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is an uncommon English word deriving from the Yiddish word for to drag and means to move something from one place to another with difficulties.", "correct_answer": "Schlep", "incorrect_answers": ["Kibbitz", "Glitch", "Maven"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which engineer founded the Institution of Mechanical Engineers in 1847?", "correct_answer": "George Stephenson", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Stephenson", "Igor Sikorski", "Joseph Strauss"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the natural habitat of sloths?", "correct_answer": "Central and South America", "incorrect_answers": ["Central and South Asia", "Australia and the island of Tasmania", "South Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A song by what famous rapper was featured in the soundtrack of the G-Force 2009 movie?", "correct_answer": "Flo Rida", "incorrect_answers": ["Eminem", "Lloyd Banks", "The Game"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which part of a building is also a computer operating system name?", "correct_answer": "Windows", "incorrect_answers": ["Doors", "Balcony", "Loggia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This person, who was High King of Ireland from 1002 to 1014, is popular as the ruler who managed to unify the regional leaders of Ireland, in order to free the land from Danish occupation.", "correct_answer": "Brian Boru", "incorrect_answers": ["Henry II", "Campbell of Munster", "Patrick of Kearney"]}]